Guide to the John Henry and Anna Botsford Comstock papers, 1833-1955,
Comstock, John Henry and Anna Botsford papers,
- Correspondence
  - John Henry Comstock professional correspondence
    - M-R
      - National Express Co., 1894-03-19 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Needham, James George, 1896-02-20 (Box 6, Folder 14)
        Entomologist; Profesoor of Biology, Lake Forrest; Professor, Cornell University
      - Needham, James George, 1896-05-11 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Needham, James George, 1896-05-21 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Needham, James George, 1896-05-25 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Needham, James George, 1896-06-05 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Needham, James George, 1898-10-04 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Needham, James George, 1898-11-28 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - Needham, James George, 1900-04-27 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Needham, James George, 1900-05-14 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - New England Farmer, 1886-11-20 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - New York Association of Cornell University, 1886-03-31 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - New York, Lake Erie and Western R.R. Co., 1891-11-17 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Newbury, Clara White, 1891-12-22 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Newbury, Clara White, 1893-09-08 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Newbury, S.B., 1890-02-20 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Newcomb, Herman Danforth, 1892-06-09 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Newman, Jared Treman, 1886-04-20 (Box 2, Folder 12)
        Lawyer, Cornell Trustee
      - Newman, Jared Treman, 1887-05-07 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Newman, Jared Treman, 1889-09-10 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - Newman, Jared Treman, 1889-10-24 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Newman, Jared Treman, 1890-07-09 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Newman, Jared Treman, 1890-09-14 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Newman, Jared Treman, 1890-09-17 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Newman, Jared Treman, 1890-10-16 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Newman, Jared Treman, 1890-12-31 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Newman, Jared Treman, 1891-10-13 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Newman, Jared Treman, 1891-10-20 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Newman, Jared Treman, 1891-10-28 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Newman, Jared Treman, 1891-10-31 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Newman, Jared Treman, 1891-11-25 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Newman, Jared Treman, 1891-12-10 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Newman, Jared Treman, 1891-12-14 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Newman, Jared Treman, 1892-02-02 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Newman, Jared Treman, 1892-04-18 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Newman, Jared Treman, 1892-05-02 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Newman, Jared Treman, 1892-05-21 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Newman, Jared Treman, 1892-06-18 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Newman, Jared Treman, 1892-07-13 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Newman, Jared Treman, 1892-07-14 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Newman, Jared Treman, 1892-07-18 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Newman, Jared Treman, 1892-07-23 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Newman, Jared Treman, 1892-08-01 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Newman, Jared Treman, 1892-08-06 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Newman, Jared Treman, 1892-08-13 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Newman, Jared Treman, 1892-08-15 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Newman, Jared Treman, 1892-08-17 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Newman, Jared Treman, 1892-08-31 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Newman, Jared Treman, 1892-11-08 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Newman, Jared Treman, 1892-11-18 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Newman, Jared Treman, 1892-12-07 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Newman, Jared Treman, 1893-10-26 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Newstead, Robert, 1889-10-22 (Box 3, Folder 15)
        Curator, Grosvenor Museum Of Natural History
      - Newstead, Robert, 1889-12-09 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Newstead, Robert, 1891-07-31 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Newstead, Robert, 1891-09-24 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - Nichols, G.E., 1889-05-08 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Niles, William, 1887-10-18 (Box 2, Folder 25)
        former student, JHC; friend
      - Nobile, A.A., 1885-12-19 (Box 2, Folder 8)
        Teacher, French and Italian
      - Norman, W.W., 1892-07-02 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Northrup, L.H., 1894-04-27 (Box 6, Folder 8)
        asking references from JHC for Mr. O'Neil and Mr. Russell to job of school principal
      - Norton, James, 1890-10-20 (Box 4, Folder 4)
        farmer
      - Norton, James, 1890-10-25 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Norton, James, 1890-11-05 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Norton, James, 1890-11-08 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Norton, James, 1890-11-12 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Nugent, J. Oliver, 1898 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Nugent, J. Oliver, 1898-10-11 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Oakes and Burger, 1890-05-14 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Oakes, F.S., 1889-01-19 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Olive, Edgar William, 1893-09-19 (Box 5, Folder 21)
        botany
      - O'Neill, James, 1891-10-31 (Box 4, Folder 16)
        lawyer
      - Orange Judd Co., 1898-09-29 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Ormeroner, Elanor A., 1886-12-06 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - Osborn, Herbert, 1881-10-25 (Box 2, Folder 2)
        Zoology and entomology; Iowa Agricultural College
      - Osborn, Herbert, 1887-10-20 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Osborn, Herbert, 1890-12-30 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Osborn, Herbert, 1893-09-12 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Osborn, Herbert, 1894-02-01 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Osborn, Herbert, 1894-02-09 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Osborne, Charles Francis, 1892-07-01 (Box 5, Folder 10)
        Professor of Architecture, Cornell
      - Ossendauer, R., 1882-04-22 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Ostrander and Hunt, 1885-10-14 (Box 2, Folder 7)
        meat dealers
      - Ostrander and Hunt, 1885-11-15 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Ostrander and Hunt, 1885-12-14 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Ostrander and Hunt, 1886-10-15 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Ostrander and Hunt, 1886-11-15 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Ostrander and Hunt, 1886-12-18 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - Ostrander and Hunt, Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Otis, R.C., 1889-05-28 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Otis, R.C., 1889-06-10 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Outlook Co., 1893-11-09 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Outram, Thomas Sidney, 1886-11-08 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Overacker, H., 1892-03-01 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Overman Wheel Co., 1892-01-22 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Oviatt, David Brainerd, 1886-09-11 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - Oxer, Rosa Lee, 1891-04-25 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Packard, Allyn Augustus, 1886-01-18 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Packard, Allyn Augustus, 1886-07-18 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Packard, Allyn Augustus, 1886-09-29 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - Packard, Allyn Augustus, 1887-04-21 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Packard, Allyn Augustus, 1887-05-29 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Packard, Allyn Augustus, 1887-06-30 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Packard, Allyn Augustus, 1888-09-06 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Packard, Allyn Augustus, 1890-07-09 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Packard, Allyn Augustus, 1892-12-07 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Packard, J.C., 1890-05-25 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Panton, J.H., 1890-03-20 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - Panton, J.H., 1890-11-05 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Panton, J.H., 1892-05-31 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Panton, J.H., 1893-03-16 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - Park and Tilford, 1899-10-24 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Parke, Davis and Co., 1886-03-16 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Parker, E.H., 1885-04-02 (Box 2, Folder 4)
        student
      - Parker, M.E., 1885-10-13 (Box 2, Folder 7)
        Library Bureau, Boston
      - Parker, W.E., 1891-06-04 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Parker, Wilber F., 1892-02-22 (Box 5, Folder 5)
        Horticultural Commissioner
      - Parr, Raymond, 1896-07-27 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Parr, Samuel Wilson, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
        Chemistry
      - Paterson, B. Eaton, 1889-06-13 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Patrick, George Edward, 1891-10-06 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Patton, W.N., 1888-01-26 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Patton, W.N., 1889-02-05 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - Patton, W.N., 1889-02-06 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - Paull, H.A., 1887-05-20 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Paull, H.A., 1891-05-29 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Payne, D.B., 1891-08-26 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Pazetti, Pargiori, 1889-12-30 (Box 3, Folder 17)
        Director, Agricultural Entomological Station, Florence, Italy
      - Peabody, Selim Hobart, 1886-01-22 (Box 2, Folder 9)
        President., University of Illinois
      - Pearce, Otis Ezra, 1886-06-01 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - Pearce, Otis Ezra, 1886-09-11 (Box 2, Folder 17)
        obituary
      - Pearsall, N.B., 1889-04-03 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - Pearson, Edward Jones, 1890-10-17 (Box 4, Folder 4)
        R.R. official
      - Pearson, Henry G., 1889-05-17 (Box 3, Folder 10)
        from Committee to erect monument to HGP, late Postmaster of NYC
      - Peck, H.A., 1887-05-09 (Box 2, Folder 23)
        Henry Allen?, Astron.
      - Peck, H.A., 1888-10-28 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Peckinson, E.G., 1890-07-04 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Pergande, Theodore, 1890-02-19 (Box 3, Folder 19)
        Asst., Entomoloy Division, U.S. Department of Agriculture
      - Pergande, Theodore, 1890-03-12 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - Pergande, Theodore, 1892-02-12 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Pergande, Theodore, 1893-10-30 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Pergande, Theodore, 1894-04-30 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Perkins, Albert J., 1890-10-12 (Box 4, Folder 4)
        Jackson and Perkins, Rose/Clem. Growers
      - Perkins, Albert J., 1891-08-18 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Perkins, Albert J., 1891-09-06 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - Perkins, C.H., 1890-01-20 (Box 3, Folder 18)
        Dried Fruits, Rose/Clem. Growers
      - Perkins, C.H., 1890-02-24 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Perkins, C.H., 1890-03-03 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - Perkins, C.H., 1890-04-01 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - Perkins, C.H., 1890-05-01 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Perkins, C.H., 1890-05-08 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Perkins, C.H., 1890-09-03 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Perkins, C.H., 1891-05-21 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Perkins, J.N., 1889-07-13 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Perry, F.G., 1888-02-24 (Box 2, Folder 27)
        The Educatnl. Supply Co., Boston
      - Perry, T.A., 1891-02-11 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Pettit, Rufus Hiram, 1891-08-18 (Box 4, Folder 14)
        Entomologist.; illustrator for JHC textbook
      - Pettit, Rufus Hiram, 1891-08-29 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Pettit, Rufus Hiram, 1891-09-18 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - Pettit, Rufus Hiram, 1891-11-19 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Pettit, Rufus Hiram, 1891-12-16 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Pettit, Rufus Hiram, 1891-12-21 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Pettit, Rufus Hiram, 1892-01-13 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Pettit, Rufus Hiram, 1892-04-03 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Pettit, Rufus Hiram, 1899-03-28 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Phelps, George, 1889-10-23 (Box 3, Folder 15)
        Harwood?
        lawyer, NYC)
      - Phillips, Anna D., 1890-05-24 (Box 3, Folder 22)
        for C.O. Whitman, Dir., Marine Bio. Lab., Woods Holl
      - Phillips, E.J., 1889-06-06 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Phillips, F.W., 1890-02-01 (Box 3, Folder 19)
        Real estate
      - Phillips, F.W., 1890-03-04 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - Phillips, F.W., 1890-07-14 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Phillips, F.W., 1891-10-16 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Phillips, F.W., 1893-04-06 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - Phillips, R.A., 1890-03-01 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - Phillips, Sarah Triphena, 1887-10-12 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Phillips, Sarah Triphena, 1887-10-19 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Phillips, Sarah Triphena, 1888-04-10 (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Phillips, Sarah Triphena, 1889-05-11 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Phillips, Sarah Triphena, 1890-03-08 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - Phillips, Sarah Triphena, 1891-03-28 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Phillips, Sarah Triphena, 1891-04-30 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Phillips, Sarah Triphena, 1891-06-21 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Photoengraving Co., 1886-03-07 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Photoengraving Co., 1888-02-20 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Photoengraving Co., 1888-03-23 (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - Photoengraving Co., 1888-03-26 (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - Pickering, F.E., 1890-06-01 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - Pickering, F.E., 1891-04-01 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Pickering, F.E., Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Pierson, R.R., 1890-02-03 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Pitts, Eva Maria, 1887-06 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Pitts, Eva Maria, 1887-06-14 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Pitts, Eva Maria, 1896-10-05 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Platts, A.H. and Co., 1893-02-20 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Pleasant Valley Wine Co., 1893-05-26 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Pleasant Valley Wine Co., 1893-08-14 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - Pleasant Valley Wine Co., 1893-08-16 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - Plumb, Charles Sumner, 1886-11-24 (Box 2, Folder 19)
        Animal Husbandry; NY Experiment Station
      - Plumb, Charles Sumner, 1887-01-31 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Plumb, Charles Sumner, 1889-05-27 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Plumb, Charles Sumner, 1891-09-25 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - Plumb, Charles Sumner, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Political Science Quarterly, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Pool, S.V., 1891-12-07 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Popenoe, E.A., 1896-05-15 (Box 6, Folder 14)
        Professor Horticulture and Entomology
      - Popular Gardening, 1888-09-27 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Post Office, 1886-03-11 (Box 2, Folder 11)
        Receipts, money orders, etc.
      - Post Office, 1891-11-03 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Post Office, 1892-04-28 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Post Office, 1892-12-17 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Poteat, William Louis, 1888-10-30 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Powell, George T., 1890-03-17 (Box 3, Folder 20)
        Fruit Grower; Director, Farmers' Insts.
      - Powell, George T., 1890-06-06 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - Powell, George T., 1890-10-10 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Powell, George T., 1890-10-17 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Powell, George T., 1890-11-12 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Powell, George T., 1891-02-09 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Powell, George T., 1891-02-13 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Powell, George T., 1891-05-03 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Powell, George T., 1891-05-30 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Powell, George T., 1891-09-11 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - Powell, George T., 1892-07-11 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Powell, George T., 1894-09-02 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Powell, George T., 1896-08-11 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Powell, George T., 1900-07-25 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Powell, George T., Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Power, S.C., 1891-01-07 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Pratt, Harry, 1889-05-12 (Box 3, Folder 10)
        Henry Sherring
        Zool., Haverford)
      - Pratt, Harry, 1889-10-26 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Pratt, Harry, 1891-06 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Pratt, Harry, 1892-10 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - Pratt, Harry, 1892-11-01 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Pratt, Harry, 1893-08-18 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - Pratt, Harry, 1899-03-27 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Pratt, Harry, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Pratt, Mary H., 1898-07-21 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Pratt, Mary H., 1901-07-24 (Box 6, Folder 22)
      - Prentiss, Adeline Eldred, 1891-03-18 (Box 4, Folder 9)
        Mrs. Lucien A. Wait
        Recpt. To ABC for donation to Charity Kindergarten, Ithaca)
      - Prentiss, Albert Nelson, 1887-12-09 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Prentiss, Albert Nelson, 1892-08-01 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Prentiss, Albert Nelson, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Preston, Evenezer Jewett, 1890-12-31 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Price, R.H., 1892-08-03 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Prosser, Charles Smith, 1892-09-11 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Publishers Weekly, 1891-07-01 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Publishers Weekly, 1891-08-26 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Publishers Weekly, 1891-08-31 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Publishers Weekly, 1892-08-19 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Puffer, Mrs. L.C., 1890-05-12 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Putnam, Frederic Ward, 1886-08-24 (Box 2, Folder 16)
        Anthropology and Zoology
      - Putnam, Frederic Ward, 1886-11-21 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Putnam, Frederic Ward, 1887-02-26 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Putnams Sons, 1892-08-23 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Putney, E.D., 1890-03-04 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - Putney, E.D., 1890-03-15 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - Quajat, Enrico D., 1899-03-07 (Box 6, Folder 19)
        Padova, Italy, Experimental Station
      - Quajat, Enrico D., 1899-05-19 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Queen, James W. and Company, 1888-05-01 (Box 2, Folder 30)
        Math/Optical instruments
      - Queen, James W. and Company, 1888-05-10 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Queen, James W. and Company, 1888-05-16 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Queen, James W. and Company, 1888-05-17 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Queen, James W. and Company, 1888-06-19 (Box 2, Folder 31)
      - Queen, James W. and Company, 1888-06-22 (Box 2, Folder 31)
      - Queen, James W. and Company, 1888-06-25 (Box 2, Folder 31)
      - Queen, James W. and Company, 1888-06-27 (Box 2, Folder 31)
      - Queen, James W. and Company, 1889-03-18 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Queen, James W. and Company, 1889-05-07 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Queen, James W. and Company, 1889-05-21 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Queen, James W. and Company, 1889-07-20 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Queen, James W. and Company, 1890-04-25 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - Queen, James W. and Company, 1891-05-02 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Queen, James W. and Company, 1891-05-18 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Queen, James W. and Company, 1891-05-27 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Queen, James W. and Company, 1891-06-05 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Queen, James W. and Company, 1891-07-09 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Queen, James W. and Company, 1891-07-17 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Queen, James W. and Company, 1891-08-11 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Queen, James W. and Company, 1891-11-07 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Queen, James W. and Company, 1892-06-01 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Queen, James W. and Company, 1892-06-13 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Queen, James W. and Company, 1892-06-17 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Queen, James W. and Company, 1892-10-29 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - Quelle, J.A., 1893-02-01 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Ragonot, E.L., 1884-06-05 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Randolph, David, 1886-11-16 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Rane, Frank William, 1892-08-03 (Box 5, Folder 11)
        Boston Gardening Co.
      - Rane, Frank William, 1892-12-09 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Rankin, George and Son, 1888-06-26 (Box 2, Folder 31)
        Glass and Earthenware
      - Rankin, George and Son, 1888-10-12 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Rankin, George and Son, 1890-03-22 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - Rankin, George and Son, 1890-06-25 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - Ransom, Mrs. C.A., 1891-10-09 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Ransom, Mrs. C.A., 1891-10-15 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Rappleye, A.J., 1890-01-27 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Rathay, G., 1898-05-31 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Rathay, G., Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Rathbun, Richard, 1891-05-01 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Rathbun, Richard, 1891-05-20 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Reed, Ellen, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Reed, William H., 1894-01-01 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Region, Emily S., 1888-11-03 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Reid, Harold Newton, 1891-09-14 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - Remington, N.C., 1889-06-12 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Resdon, F.A., 1888-07-24 (Box 2, Folder 32)
      - Reynolds, Lang, 1892-01-15 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Rice, George C., Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Rice, James Edward, 1890-06-25 (Box 3, Folder 23)
        Poulty husbandry, Cornell University
      - Rice, James Edward, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Rich, Benjamin, 1886-12-16 (Box 2, Folder 20)
        Tailor
      - Richardson, James, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
        American Museum of Natural History
      - Richardson, W.R., 1888-10-12 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Ricksecker, L.E., 1893-02-23 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Ricksecker, L.E., 1894-01-27 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Ricksecker, L.E., 1894-02-23 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Righter, F.M., 1892-02-16 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Righter, F.M., 1892-03-02 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Riley, Charles Valentine, 1878-11-27 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Riley, Charles Valentine, 1882-06-22 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Riley, Charles Valentine, 1885-05-07 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Riley, Charles Valentine, 1886-11-08 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Riley, Charles Valentine, 1886-11-18 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Riley, Charles Valentine, 1886-12-21 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - Riley, Charles Valentine, 1887-07-31 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Riley, Charles Valentine, 1887-10-31 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Riley, Charles Valentine, 1888-03-02 (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - Riley, Charles Valentine, 1888-03-26 (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - Riley, Charles Valentine, 1888-05-19 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Riley, Charles Valentine, 1888-09-20 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Riley, Charles Valentine, 1888-10-06 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Riley, Charles Valentine, 1888-10-09 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Riley, Charles Valentine, 1890-01-06 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Riley, Charles Valentine, 1890-05-10 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Riley, Charles Valentine, 1890-09-16 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Riley, Charles Valentine, 1890-09-20 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Riley, Charles Valentine, 1890-09-23 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Riley, Charles Valentine, 1890-10-16 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Riley, Charles Valentine, 1891-08-19 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Riley, Charles Valentine, 1891-11-19 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Riley, Charles Valentine, 1893-10-03 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Riley, William Albert, 1890-01-02 (Box 3, Folder 18)
        Professor of Zoology
      - Riley, William Albert, 1898-06-03 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Ringler and Company, F.A., 1888-02-16 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Ritchie, E.S. and Sons, 1888-05-11 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Ritzemassos, J., 1898-11-12 (Box 6, Folder 18)
        Amsterdam, Netherlands
      - Rivers, J.J., 1887-10-20 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Roberts, Isaac Phillips, 1886-01-21 (Box 2, Folder 9)
        Cornell dairy
      - Roberts, Isaac Phillips, 1886-01-26 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Roberts, Isaac Phillips, 1886-02-05 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Roberts, Isaac Phillips, 1888-04-16 (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Roberts, Isaac Phillips, 1890-10-01 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Roberts, Isaac Phillips, 1891-03-01 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Roberts, Isaac Phillips, 1891-09-01 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - Roberts, Isaac Phillips, 1891-10-01 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Roberts, Isaac Phillips, 1891-10-19 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Roberts, Isaac Phillips, 1891-11-01 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Roberts, Isaac Phillips, 1891-12-01 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Roberts, Isaac Phillips, 1892-04-20 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Roberts, Isaac Phillips, 1892-05-20 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Roberts, Isaac Phillips, 1893-12-20 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Roberts, Isaac Phillips, 1894-02-01 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Roberts, Kittie E., 1892-07-14 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Roberts, Kittie E., 1892-08-14 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Roberts, Kittie E., 1892-11-13 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Robertson, Charles, 1894-03-12 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Robertson, J.W., 1889-12-27 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Robinson, James A., 1892-09-27 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Robinson, W.G., 1896-09-03 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Robinson, William H., 1891-08-06 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Robinson, William H., 1891-08-18 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Rodman, Washington, 1890-10-09 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Rodman, Washington, 1890-12-11 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Rodman, Washington, 1890-12-24 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Rogers, Julius Edwin, 1889-01-10 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Rogers, Julius Edwin, 1889-05-13 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Rolfe, Henry Winchester, 1885-09-23 (Box 2, Folder 6)
        Instructor Swarthmore; wife graduate Of Cornell